<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Kevin Gibson</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Kevin Gibson</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 10 Feb 2017 12:22:17 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Command Streams with Lambda Functions</title>
      <link>/blog/command-streams-with-lambda-functions/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Feb 2017 12:22:17 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/command-streams-with-lambda-functions/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;ve been working on a rendering backend to make creating quick-and-dirty OpenGL projects easier - basically a simple game engine that I&amp;rsquo;m comfortable breaking apart and toying with. Right now I&amp;rsquo;m splitting off my OpenGL backend to run on a separate thread, so that while the engine is simulating frame N+1, the render thread is drawing frame N. Since I don&amp;rsquo;t want to have a massive sync point between the two threads, and I don&amp;rsquo;t want to surround everything in mutexes, I&amp;rsquo;ll need to have two copies of a lot of data: one that is owned by the render thread, and one that is owned by the game thread.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>about</title>
      <link>/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Aug 2016 13:01:22 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/about/</guid>
      <description>I am a software engineer at Microsoft, working primarily on Spatial Mapping for Hololens. I got my Masters in Computer Science from the University of Toronto in 2016, and my graduated from the Mathematics and Engineering program at Queen&amp;rsquo;s University in 2014. Originally from Toronto, I now live in Seattle. I&amp;rsquo;m interested in a variety of areas of computer graphics, including geometry processing, rendering, and physical simulation. Outside of research I&amp;rsquo;m also interested in music, good beer, and cooking.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>